{
  "extraDescription": "for nonnegative fractions, in which the denominators are the same or one of the denominators is 1",
  "openingRemarks": "NB: you can give answers as unsimplified fractions.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{11} \\div \\dfrac{9}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{6} \\div 1\\)",
      "answer": "1/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{12} \\times \\dfrac{7}{12}\\)",
      "answer": "77/144",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{5} \\div \\dfrac{11}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{9} \\times \\dfrac{7}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "49/81",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 \\div \\dfrac{9}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 \\div \\dfrac{1}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{7} \\div \\dfrac{9}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "8/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{7} \\div \\dfrac{1}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{6}{7} \\times 0\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 \\div \\dfrac{11}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "2/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{4} \\div \\dfrac{3}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "5/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{8} \\div \\dfrac{5}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 \\div \\dfrac{3}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 \\div \\dfrac{7}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "10/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{7} \\times \\dfrac{9}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "9/49",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{8} \\div \\dfrac{5}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "11/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{4} \\div \\dfrac{5}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "11/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{6} \\times \\dfrac{11}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "121/36",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 \\times \\dfrac{10}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 \\times \\dfrac{2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{3} \\times 1\\)",
      "answer": "11/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 \\times \\dfrac{7}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "7/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{6}{7} \\times \\dfrac{12}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "72/49",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{5} \\times \\dfrac{2}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "6/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{6}{11} \\times \\dfrac{1}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "6/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{5} \\times \\dfrac{7}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "56/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{3} \\times \\dfrac{2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "4/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{2} \\div \\dfrac{5}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "7/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{5} \\times 1\\)",
      "answer": "2/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{7} \\div 0\\)",
      "answer": "undefined",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 \\times \\dfrac{5}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "5/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{6} \\div \\dfrac{1}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{7} \\div \\dfrac{11}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "2/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{4} \\times \\dfrac{11}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "11/16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{10} \\times 1\\)",
      "answer": "3/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{5} \\times \\dfrac{6}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "48/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{2} \\times \\dfrac{9}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "63/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{11} \\times \\dfrac{9}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "63/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{5} \\div \\dfrac{6}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{9} \\times \\dfrac{5}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "10/81",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{3} \\times \\dfrac{11}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "121/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 \\div \\dfrac{6}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "7/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 \\div \\dfrac{11}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "27/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{7} \\times \\dfrac{5}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "55/49",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{2} \\times 0\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{6}{11} \\div \\dfrac{2}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{2}{5} \\times 2\\)",
      "answer": "4/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{2} \\div \\dfrac{11}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "9/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{6} \\times \\dfrac{5}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "25/36",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{3} \\div \\dfrac{11}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "7/11",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(11 \\div \\dfrac{4}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "33/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{2} \\times \\dfrac{9}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "99/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 \\div \\dfrac{7}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{11} \\div \\dfrac{6}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "7/6",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{11} \\div \\dfrac{9}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{7} \\times \\dfrac{4}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "12/49",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{2} \\times 0\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 \\div \\dfrac{1}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{2} \\times 3\\)",
      "answer": "21/2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 \\div \\dfrac{2}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{12}{5} \\div \\dfrac{12}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 \\div \\dfrac{1}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{2} \\times 2\\)",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 \\div \\dfrac{3}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "88/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{6}{5} \\times 0\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{3} \\div 4\\)",
      "answer": "1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{11} \\times \\dfrac{5}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "35/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 \\times \\dfrac{3}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{5} \\times \\dfrac{1}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "1/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{4} \\times \\dfrac{1}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "5/16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 \\times \\dfrac{5}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 \\div \\dfrac{10}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "7/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{6}{5} \\times \\dfrac{6}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "36/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{8} \\times \\dfrac{11}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "55/64",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 \\times \\dfrac{11}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "22/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{10}{3} \\times 4\\)",
      "answer": "40/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{3} \\div 3\\)",
      "answer": "7/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4 \\div \\dfrac{3}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "8/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3} \\div \\dfrac{4}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "1/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{10}{3} \\times 3\\)",
      "answer": "10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{6}{5} \\times \\dfrac{4}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "24/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{3} \\times \\dfrac{11}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "77/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{12}{7} \\times \\dfrac{10}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "120/49",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(11 \\div \\dfrac{11}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "2",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{9} \\times \\dfrac{5}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "35/81",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 \\times \\dfrac{1}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "1/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{11} \\div \\dfrac{5}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "3/5",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{7} \\times 1\\)",
      "answer": "9/7",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{10} \\times 1\\)",
      "answer": "1/10",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{4} \\times \\dfrac{1}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "1/16",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3} \\times \\dfrac{4}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "4/9",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{7} \\times \\dfrac{6}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "66/49",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{5} \\times \\dfrac{6}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "6/25",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{11} \\times \\dfrac{9}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "45/121",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{11} \\div \\dfrac{6}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "2/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{10}{7} \\div \\dfrac{8}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "5/4",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{7} \\times \\dfrac{1}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "5/49",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 \\div \\dfrac{3}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "10/3",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{10} \\div 0\\)",
      "answer": "undefined",
      "numberInputTypes": ["mix", "cfr"]
    }
  ]
}
